Hello there!
Things have finally calmed down,
probably because it's so late at night.
There's nothing to do and no
one to talk to at this hour.
I guess I could check on my stats
since I haven't done that in a while.
Maybe I'll start by reviewing
all my vending machine types.
Vending machines are largely
divided into two categories.
Those that sell goods, and
those with automated services.
The first category is
pretty self-explanatory.
Those machines sell all kinds of things.
Even just within the food and drink
category, you've got sodas, coffee, alcohol,
milk drinks, candy, cooking
products, frozen desserts, etc.
Then there are cigarettes,
tickets, postcards,
postage stamps of all kinds, newspapers,
magazines, you name it.
It's gonna be another one.
Hello there.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Next, you've got automated service
machines, which include all kinds of stuff,
like money-changing machines
and pachinko ball dispensers.
There's been intense
discourse over whether these
automated service units
are vending machines?
But in my opinion if you pay a
machine to vend a thing it counts!
That must be why power
washer is in my function
list and I only just
recently noticed this.
But rank 3 has been added to that list.
I guess that means I still have room to
grow in my journey as a vending machine
To attain rank 3 I would
need 3 million points.
I don't even know what
that would let me do
But I'm grateful.
I get to chase my vending machine dreams
Having goals makes me so happy.
Yeah, I know it's fried chicken,
but I can't pronounce it well so fried
chicken is what ended up sticking!
Alright, alright relax.
There's plenty to go around
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner,
Lamas.
The name's Boxo. Hello there.
That means yes, by the way.
Hume and me stayed up all night
fixing the transfer circle,
so we've started evacuating the
residents of the Origin Stratum.
Their place of refuge will be
the Clear Flow Lake Stratum.
Come to think of it, I still don't
know how many strata this dungeon has.
Horwa many?
Oh, right, how many strata?
Well, starting from the top,
there's the Origin Stratum,
the Dead's Lament Stratum, Clear Flow
Lake Stratum, The Labyrinth Stratum,
Scorching Sand Stratum, Dark Forest
Stratum, and then Dog Mountain Stratum.
That's not all.
Below that is the Everlasting
Stratum, which is yet to be conquered.
So at this point, we know there
are at least eight stratum.
Alright, let's begin the evacuation.
Well, the transfer circle
seems to be working just fine.
Raises the question, what
do we do with it after this?
If we just abandon it and
the monsters misuse it,
it'll cause a lot of
trouble for other strata.
We could hunt down the
Netherlord's underling
and break their control over the monsters.
That would solve the problem.
Theoretically, yes.
But I can't afford to spare the manpower
it would require to hunt them down.
Well, in that case, how about
trusting the hunting parts,
the esteemed menagerie of
fools and band of gluttons.
Does he think being
dashing will have his case?
You're willing to do that?
I'd be happy to.
I want to gather more info
on the Neverborn anyway.
That said, it's going to cost you.
Fair enough.
The better the results,
the higher the reward.
He was going to do it even
if she refused to pay.
Mishuel's really got the moves, huh, Akka?
Yeah, sure wish we had a
flashy attack like that.
Oh, water, become Whirlpools and fear!
Incredible fighting there, everyone.
Boxxo, might I trouble you for
a little something to drink?
You're not fighting?
No, seeing how my primary function is
healing, I have no arsenal of offensive magic,
which essentially means I
am a bystander in combat.
We each have our own roles to play.
I'm not sure if he's serious or not.
Heavy's face is particularly hard to read.
Now, which way do we go?
The map says there's a small
lake not far ahead to the right.
On the other hand, if we
go left, it's a long haul,
and there's a three-way
split in the path from there.
I think we should check out the
lake first, but from there, uh...
What's that?
Can't we just pause to chat
without some jerks showing up?
Huh?
Heavy, what are you doing?
It's dangerous to get that close!
Pay it no mind.
Heavy, hold your horses!
Fret not, Captain.
I'll handle this. Okay, fine.
Suit yourself.
What's up with that?
What are they looking around for?
Why aren't the monsters attacking?
I'll bet they might see walls that
are invisible to us. That's correct.
Heavy excels in magic
that manipulates light.
This allows him to produce illusions,
and he's also able to influence
the mind more directly.
Oh, right.
Like when he hid those
people in the prison.
I have no interest in those who go
barefoot, so there's no need to spare these.
He has the blessing of might too,
though I will say it's not
as strong as Llama says.
Whoa, no mercy!
I think it's safe to say
Heavy's got this handled.
Right, I think we should
split up into two groups.
It would be pretty dumb if we
all searched in one direction
and they got past us just by
coming from the other way.
If it's all the same to you, Captain,
I wish to accompany the lake group.
All right, where should we go, Boxo?
Hmm, I'm concerned for
everyone in the heavy group.
If I had to choose...
That took way.
Oh, you want to go to the lake?
Sure, sounds good.
Alrighty then, Captain,
we're going to the lake too.
Good grief.
This search party only
includes half our members,
but we managed to wipe
these guys out in no time.
Wow, the lake water's
crystal clear. My friends,
we seem to be making excellent time,
so why don't you all take a
break and get in the water?
Ugh, majorly sus.
The others are waiting on us,
so we'd better hurry back
the captain said we needed to
be back in about three hours
And we're well within that.
Yeah, you're right.
He did say that.
I don't know you guys
can stand there debating
Yeah, I'm with you
No, they seem tempted to
join in danger ladies.
Don't worry girls.
I will be right here on the shore standing
guard I think even just dipping your
feet in the water and washing your hair
would make you feel quite refreshed.
Yeah, that sounds nice.
Want to, Lamas? Well, okay.
A little dip can't hurt, right?
Wait here for a bit, Boxo.
And...
form change!
Oh, my.
This is no place to leave these.
Someone might come along and steal them.
I had better keep an eye
out while the girls swim.
Though I can't help but wonder,
what do both their shoes smell like?
I called it! Too bad!
Saw that coming from a mile away.
Why don't you get some
refreshment too, Heavy?
And wash your dirty
mind while you're at it.
Hey, we're back! Hi there!
Oh, glad to see you all.
Um, Heavy, why are you soaking wet?
I just fell in the lake for
purely personal reasons.
I'm leaving that one alone.
I believe it's about time for lunch.
Boxo, if you would.
I'd be happy to.
In fact, I want to try out a new function
I think you guys will appreciate.
Form change!
It's a vending machine
market where you can
buy convenient store items 24 hours a day.
And I get to show off my knack for
arranging things with limited space.
Okay, so here's the ideal lineup.
Come taste the wonders of a vending
machine-turned-mini-convenient store!
Wow!
That is a treasure trove of delight!
Yeah, there are foods in there
I've never even heard of before!
That means I'll just have to try them all!
Seriously, it all looks
freaking delicious!
Yes, we will have to sample
everything, won't we?
Where should we start, Akka?
Let's each choose different
items and then go halfsy, Shiro!
Oh wait, they probably don't know how to
open a rice ball, so I should demonstrate.
Pardon me, comrades?
I do apologize, but like that,
can I get some help over here?
I'm fatiguing and alarming right here.
Boxo, Boxo.
Boxo.
Hold it!
We'll probably find them
somewhere down this hill.
Yes, most likely.
Mishuel, can you tell how many
beings might be down there?
They're too close together
for me to count accurately.
That being said, we should be
prepared for at least a hundred.
Oh, that's all? Good.
We won't get our butts handed to
us even if we charge right in.
Mishuel, you and I will take the lead.
Yeah, that's fine by me.
Is there anything I can do?
Could I slow down the monsters somehow?
Oh, I know just the thing!
Form change!
Oh, Boxo, what's going on?
This is kind of incredible!
Master Boxo, can you tell
me what these balls are?
Too close for comfort there, Mishuel.
So then,
if they try to charge, they'll just slip
on these little balls and fall down?
Cut off. Act.
We should declare Lamas the
official Boxxo interpreter.
I think I hear monsters
screaming from that way.
They sound weird, though,
and there's lots of noise.
Good.
Seems like Boxxo set the stage for us.
Let's get in there, people!
Yes, sir!
If there's this many of them,
I bet the commander's in there somewhere!
Let the battle begin!
Roaring strike!
If I could only grow to
be as strong as Mishuel,
I just know I'd be a lot more help
to everyone in times like these.
You're fine, Lamas.
Right, I'd better get busy. Recently,
I realized I can switch out
goods to get access to this
candy without turning into the
specialized vending machine.
You never know these
things unless you try.
Launch!
Boxxo, can you maybe handle
the enemies behind us?
Hello there!
Letting me cover her back
is proof that she trusts me.
It's a man's job to live up to that!
I now know that this works
great as a blunt weapon.
So I'll use it to take out any enemy
that tries to attack llamas from behind.
Glory! Strike!
They just keep coming.
We can't win if new guys keep showing
up as fast as we can take them out.
We need to locate the commander somehow.
I might as well try asking Lamas.
Lam is... You called? Ah!
Us, the people, they're there!
Uh, wait, you want me
to throw you over there?
No way! I can't!
I don't want to use you like
you're just some object!
You're a-perton-er. Partner?
Yeah, we are partners, huh?
Well, as your partner,
allow me to say this.
No!
Oh!
Voxor, are you trying to put yourself
in harm's way out of concern for me?
Here I am, doing the same thing.
I never want you to get hurt,
and I'd do anything to stop it.
Yeah, you're right.
Suori, be!
No need to apologize.
Our hearts beat as one after all.
I attack, and you defend!
Together, we can do anything! Yes!
From now on, we'll work together.
We'll determine a suitable
strategy for every situation.
And so, let's work together now.
We can launch a suicide attack!
I'm sorry, did I hear you right?
I think that's a little
extreme, don't you?
Lamas, Master Boxo, if you're coming
through, allow me to clear a path.
Master Boxo, feel free to proceed.
No, you feel free to stop us.
Thanks, Mishuel, that's Boxo's
number one offenses for you.
Oh, please, no need for flattery.
Fishwell seems bolstered
by the compliment.
Welp, here goes nothing!
To incapacitate enemies without defeating
them, that calls for pachinko balls.
The best product for slipping and
falling would have to be these. Launch!
Hey, this is kind of fun!
More balls coming at ya!
Nice.
That takes care of them.
Boxxo, where's the commander?
It's all green fiends.
I don't see anything that
looks like a commander.
Boxxo!
What the heck?
Mikenne! You okay? What happened?
Thanks, Slomus. Hey, listen.
Before, I heard what sounded like
human screams coming from over there.
I think it was inside that mound.
There's still faint moans
coming out of it. Oh, good.
That first attack must have done the job.
In that case, form change!
Power washer!
There and there, huh?
Okay, I'll go check it out.
You wait right here. Good luck!
There!
Oh, there's the commander! Good!
When all your attacks can't
stop them, you go for the ring.
That's one less thing to worry about.
Master Boxo, we cleared a path of retreat.
Right, go back to the pathway.
Now, since we've made it this
far, that's mission accomplished.
With Kerioyl here, we'll question
her once we get back to the village.
Yes, we will.
But should you be taking advantage of this
trying situation by
patting a woman's rear?
Hey, relax.
I was just caught up in the moment.
That's all.
It's not like I
premeditated it or anything.
You sure about that?
Those two are really adorable together.
What exactly is their
relationship, anyway?
Captain, you always act like this.
As vice-captain...
Aren't they too old to be fighting
like this in front of everyone, Akka?
Probably so.
It's always so embarrassing
to watch, isn't it?
What does he mean, too old?
Isn't Vice-Captain Phil
Mina pretty young, though?
Oh, you mean you didn't know?
She might look young, but she's
older than the captain, actually.
What?
There's just no way that's true.
Oh, well, the vice-captain is half
some race, one I can't remember now.
The race in question is vamp fiend, Shui.
Vamp fiend?
I've never even heard of that race.
Hold on.
From what I understand,
vamp fiends are the race that survive
by feeding on people's blood, right?
And they're all beautiful creatures
who look just like humans?
Yes, and to add to that, vamp fiends
may get nourishment in other ways.
from bodily fluids whose composition
is somewhat similar to blood.
Which is why it isn't uncommon for them
to bond with humans and have children.
Or so I believe.
So romantic!
Then those two are
destined for each other!
The blood thing doesn't bother you at all?
Lamas, that's being with a monster.
Some call it an abomination.
Seems like that's not how they
thought Lamas would react.
So what?
Just because someone's race or
appearance is different from your own,
that doesn't mean anything
about who they are as a person.
Right, Boxo?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the Menagerie of
Fools has accepted her,
so she's just the same as everyone else.
You're right.
We are a bunch of oddballs, aren't we?
I just remembered.
Don't the Menagerie of Fools members
have a few wishes they want granted?
Would it be okay for me to
ask what those wishes are?
Oh, sorry.
I forget there are things
people don't talk about.
No, it's okay.
I only have one wish.
to make tons of money that I
can use to help the orphanage.
My dream is for the
children and I to be able to
eat all the tasty food
we want every single day.
Yeah, that's a simple, Shui kind of wish.
I can share mine next if you want.
My one wish is to somehow
make Boxo human again.
Aw, that's sweet.
Oh, does that mean that you and
Boxo share the same wish, cute?
Yeah.
I have a lot of them, but
we'll leave it at that.
Since we're sharing,
I have been yearning to share my
own deepest desire with you all.
No, thank you, Heavy.
Oh, that simply won't do.
How uncouth would it be to listen
to my comrades pour out their
souls while keeping my own feelings
locked away in my heart of hearts?
My wish is to collect footwear
from all over the world?
At the moment just before it wears out.
and use said footwear to construct
a vast and ornate castle.
And for the next phase of my dream plan,
At the end of each year, I
shall tax my constituents?
collecting footwear they've worn
throughout the preceding months.
That is the most depraved
wish I've heard in a while.
Well, I guess it's our turn next.
You all probably know that Shiro and
I share a common wish as well, right?
That's right, Akka.
And so our most ardent wish is this.
To be popular with the ladies!
Well, that's rich coming
from a couple of virgins.
Too bad.
What about the captain and vice-captain?
That I don't know.
I asked them about it once upon a
time, but they dodged the question.
Yeah, same here.
And here, too.
Every person has their secrets, after all.
There is no sense in
trying to ferret them out.
Heavy can be pretty insightful when
he's not being weird about shoes.
Alright, enough chit-chat, you guys.
Hurry up if you want to get
back to the village today.
Okay.
Excellent work, all of you.
Boxo, may I trouble you to provide us with
food and drinks for a celebratory feast?
Hello there.
Oh, looks so good.
I've been waiting!
I'm so happy and fried chicken!
Amazing!
All right, now to attempt something I've
been wanting to try for a while now.
Warm change!
A rice vending machine!
Now that I have telekinesis,
I can even prepare it myself.
At least I think so.
Now, how will I cook this?
Hey, Boxo, what's this stuff?
It's cookery, right? I know!
Please, help!
Mm-hmm. Sure.
What should we do?
Form change?
A gas vending machine!
Oh, eight. There! Like this? Thank you.
Oh, this is a magic
item that produces fire.
I did get some help at the end, but
I think I can handle simple cooking.
But, Boxxo, why did you start
cooking all of a sudden?
That's a good question.
You can already dispense
all kinds of food.
How do I tell them I
tried it just for kicks?
And with that, the rice is done.
I'll go get some bowls.
I'll help you with that.
This is so tasty!
Yeah, tasty is right.
All I did was cook using my abilities.
But I'm really satisfied
with myself right now.
Oh, Boxo, thanks for all that you do.
I think I might cook
again from time to time.
I'll walk you through the same time.
How are you going?
I'll be able to walk you
through the next day.
I'll be able to change the future.
This melody is the words of the road.
We're moving on the way.
I'll be able to keep my own life.
See you
next time.
You could even win a reward.
I look forward to serving you again.